runehead.com 2005-04-05

# Runescape Tip - First Fan web site (all information regarding Magic, News, Monsters, Tutorials... QUICKLY!)

  **Tip.it Privacy Policy**

The TIP.IT system is committed to maintaining your confidence and trust, and accordingly maintains the following privacy policy to protect personal information you provide online. 

**Basic Confidentiality Policy**  

It is TIP policy that **personal information** , such as your name, postal, e-mail address or telephone number, is **private and confidential**. Accordingly, the personal information you provide is accessible _only_ by designated staff, and is used _only_ for the purposes for which you provide the information (such as to reply to your request or to handle your complaint). For example, when you file a complaint about a forum abuse, the personal information you provide will be used to process your complaint. 

_If_ you also indicate on our sites that _you would like to receive information about other TIP programs and services_ , such as links, publications or membership, your personal information will be added to appropriate TIP mailing lists. You can indicate your desire when completing a complaint form or when you send us e-mail. If at any time you change your mind and would like to add or remove your name from the TIP's mailing list, or correct your personal information we will provide automatic tools to remove it or you can email us at runescape@TIP.it

**No Release of Information to Third Parties**  

Personal information **will not be released to third parties** _except_ to further the purpose for which you provide the information, such as sending your complaint to the company for action, or if release is required by law or is pertinent to judicial or governmental investigations or proceedings. _There are no other circumstances under which we will provide an we will never sell personal information to anyone._

**Computer Tracking of Identifiable Information**  

Our computer is not set up to track, collect or distribute personal information about its visitors. It does recognize the IP home server of visitors, but not e-mail addresses. For example, we can tell which Internet Service Provider our visitors use, but not the names, addresses or other information about our visitors that would allow us to identify the particular visitors to our sites. This information is used only for internal purposes by TIP technical support staff (example, so that you cannot vote at pools from same IP more then once). 

In addition, our web sites uses third part service to collect information about the visits to our web sites and ad banner exchange. For example, they compile statistics that show the daily number of visitors to our sites, the daily requests we receive for particular files on our web sites, and what countries those requests come from. These aggregated statistics are used internally to better provide services to the public and may also be provided to others, but again, the statistics contain **no personal information** and will not be used to gather such information. We will not use any service which dont have privacy police and if you have information that a service or baner we use gather personal information please inform us at runescape@TIP.it and we will imediatly examine our relations with third part.

**Third Party Advertising**

We use BUDS INC and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click here <<http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp>>

**Third Party Cookies**  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. 

**Forums, chats ...**

This site have chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Remove of information**

We provide automatic way to remove identifying information from our database and/or possibility to select not to receive future communications on appropriate pags. You may also change/ask for removal of information previously provided by sending us email at runescape@TIP.it

* * *

This site contains links to other sites. TIP.IT staffis not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of Web sites to which we link or whic participate in our programs but arre not hosted by us.

June 25, 2004
